mainpagesite.com 2018-02-04

# Privacy policy - Main Page Site

We, Copellov Ltd. ("Copellov"), located at Geneva Place, Waterfront Drive, PO Box 3469, Road Town, Tortola, British Virgin Islands, welcome you ("User"), designated user of our website www.mainpagesite.com (the "Site").

By attempting to make any use of the Site or Services, you undertake to be bound by this Privacy Policy (“PP”), and Coppelov’s Terms of Use (collectively, the “Terms”) All capitalized terms set forth herein shall have the same meaning ascribed to them in the Terms of Use document available on the site. 

Copellov reserves the right to revise and update its privacy practices from time to time such amendments shall be posted according to the terms provided in the Terms of Use. This PP is subject to the terms set forth in the Terms of Use, and may be amended by Copellov from time to time, without any prior notice to User. Any revised version of this PP will be deemed to be applicable from the first date of its publication and User agrees to be bound by such modified terms as of the date first publicized. The User is advised to check the Site frequently for any such revised terms. 

### 1\. Information Collected

1.1. The submission of personally identifiable information is not mandatory for using the Site, Site or Service. However in some cases, information collected by the Site, Site or Services may be personally identifiable in part. This includes information such as User's name, address, date and place of birth, and other information that Copellov deems necessary to distinguish an individual’s identity. 

1.2. Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to us. Therefore, the Company does not knowingly collect or maintain information from Users who it positively knows are under the age of 13.

1.3. Copellov may collect non-personally identifiable information about Users such as sites searched, fields User clicked on, information about the User’s device and/or websites visited, and User’s IP address to gather demographic information. The User gives Copellov his or her express consent to such information.

1.4. User is advised that information which is not personally identifiable will not be treated as information of confidential nature and may be shared with third parties.

### 2\. Usage of data

2.1. Copellov mainly uses information it gathers in order to (i) provide User with content such as targeted advertisements promotional and marketing material, (ii) improve and personalize Users online experience, (iii) improve its Site and Services; and (iv) have third parties help her in the foregoing.

2.2. Copellov may also use all information it gathers according to its discretion if it reasonably believes such usage is required in order to: (a) circumvent fraud or misuse of the Site or Services; (b) carry out risk management procedures; (c) protect or defend its rights or property; (d) comply with applicable law, legal process and the Terms; and (e) protect the safety and security of users of the Site, Services or members of the public.

2.3. The User acknowledges that any information collected, if any, in connection with User's use of the Site and/or the Services may be transferred across international borders to server locations, including transfers to Copellov’s subcontractors, agents or representatives and services, or for the purposes of storing the data in the relevant databases. If User does not agree to any terms and conditions as set forth in the Terms, User must immediately stop using the Site and Services.

### 3\. Use of Cookies

3.1. Copellov uses various technologies to collect and store information concerning the Internet usage habits of the User, by using tracking technologies such as cookies or anonymous identifiers, pixels, and beacons, deployed to User's Internet device.

3.2. Cookies are small files which may be used through the Site or any of the Services enabling a Site to recognize a repeat visitor to the Site. Copellov uses cookies for various reasons, such as to provide User with easy access to Site and enabling User with better online experience by allowing Copellov to learn what Site or areas of certain Site are of interest to such User. 

3.3. If User does not wish for Copellov's Cookies to be deployed, he or she may set his or her browser to reject cookies or to notify him or her when a Site tries to deploy a cookie in his or her browser Site.

3.4. Information (including information from or about pages of social media sites User visits) is used by Copellov, or shared with third parties for various purposes such as providing User with content such as targeted advertisements promotional and marketing material. Consider the following description, if applicable:

3.4.1. A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to the Device used to access the Software. Company's computers identify User's Device by its Device Identifier. Usage Information will be non-identifying. When User downloads and uses Product the Company will also collect information from its affiliates (such as third parties providing the Third Parties Services) based upon the sites you visit, the coupons you redeem, and other web sites you may have visited or Affiliate Referral URLs and will store those Affiliate Referral URLs and a list of the third parties which provide the User with Third Party Services on the User's Internet Device to assist. Thus, assisting the Company in providing User with information, content and advertisements it believes may interest him.

3.4.2. Cookies. A cookie is a data file placed on a device when it is used to interact with the Software. The Company uses cookies to collect information for record keeping purposes, to make it easier to navigate the Software. The Company uses both “persistent cookies”. “Persistent” cookies are used to make tasks like logging into a Website easier and for counting purposes (such as counting and identifying actions made by User through the Software) by remembering the User’s login information. Persistent cookies stay on the User’s device from one session to the next. Cookies may be used for many purposes, including, without limitation, remembering the User any his preferences and tracking his visits to Web-pages, third parties sites and redemption of coupons. When User clicks on a coupon or an offer on available on the Software a cookie will be set on his Internet device to track his use and redemption of the coupon or offer. The User can choose to have his device warn him each time a persistent or session cookie is being sent. A User can choose to turn off such cookies through his browser settings. If the User chooses to disable cookies on his device, some features of the Software may not function properly.

3.4.3. Web Beacons Web Beacons are small graphic images or other web programming code (also known as “1×1 GIFs” or “clear GIFs”) may be included in the Software and the content provided therein. Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a web page or e-mail can act as a web beacon. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count users interacting with the Software, to monitor how users navigate through various Websites, or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed.

3.4.4. Web Logs. The Company logs Device Identifiers and the operating system of the User's computer and may track User's movement and redemption within the Software and Third Party Services, the pages from which the User was referred, access times and browser types in order to improve security, analyze trends and administer the Software. The Company uses this information in the aggregate to gauge the effectiveness, usage, and popularity of the Software, track information for statistical purposes, help diagnose and troubleshoot server malfunctions, analyze trends, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information and track traffic and sales to third party affiliates.

### 4\. Links to Third Party Sites

4.1. The Company uses Third-Party services such as ad servers and ad networks to serve advertisements and collect information whenever the User who interact with the Site, the Services and/or the Third Party Services. These Third Parties and the advertisers themselves may use information about the User's visits on other Websites, software and/or services in order to provide advertisements about goods and services which they believe may interest the User. In the course of serving advertisements, these Third Parties may use technology to send, directly to the User's Internet device, the advertisements and links that appear on the Site and/ or the Services. 

4.2. Third Party Analytics Technologies. The Company may use third parties’ analytic and other tools to better understand the usage of the Site and/or the Services by users and how to improve the Site and/or the Services. These third parties may use cookies, pixel tags or other technologies to collect and store anonymous information such as the time User visits certain Webpages, the Webpages visited by the User, time User spends on each Webpage, Device Identifiers, type of operating system and browser used, and Affiliate Referral URLs. These third parties will provide the Company with this information in part to help it understand and analyze shopping habits and other trends to enable it to improve its site, software and/or services. 

### 5\. International Users 

User is advised to be aware that information Company collect wills be transferred to, processed and stored in The United States of America. The data protection laws in The United States of America may differ from those of the country in which User is located, and User's Personal Information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in The United States of America according to laws of The United States of America. By using the Site and/or the Services or providing any information, User gives his consent to this transfer, processing and storage of your information in The United States of America. User also consents to the application of laws of the state of Israel in all matters concerning the Site and this Privacy Policy.

6\. User is advised however his refrainment from providing the Company with certain information, may prevent him from engaging some parts of the Site and/or Services.

7\. Shall the user have any questions with regards to the Site, and/or Services, contact Copellov’s contact person via email at [admin@mainpagesite.com](mailto:admin@mainpagesite.com).
